<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Tara Pilbrow</title>
    <link>https://tarapilbrow.github.io/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Tara Pilbrow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 17:29:40 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tarapilbrow.github.io/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>taraPilbrow</title>
      <link>https://tarapilbrow.github.io/about/tarapilbrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 17:29:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tarapilbrow.github.io/about/tarapilbrow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Born in Hong Kong in 1979, Tara studied dance at Laban centre before going to Oxford to complete a degree in Chinese Studies. While in China for her degree course, Tara studied with some of Asia’s leading dance companies: Cloud Gate Dance Theatre, Taiwan; Beijing Modern Dance Company; and CCDC, Hong Kong. In Oxford, she started to work with Biserk Dance Company, with whom she continued to perform sporadically for five years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On leaving Oxford Tara spent four months in New York studying at Dance Space Center and dancing for Choreographer Juliette Mapp. She then settled in Paris where she lived for ten years, working with a number of dance companies (including Cie Jacky Auvray, Cie Longuelouve, Prisme International, Cie Gilschamber, Cie Les Orpailleurs) as well as creating her own work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She founded Tara Pilbrow Dance on her return to the UK in 2011 and created Entangled, Infanla, Waltzing Words and most recently 2+1. R&amp;amp;D for next project Stretched to the Limit starts in November 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the company</title>
      <link>https://tarapilbrow.github.io/about/company/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 07:00:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tarapilbrow.github.io/about/company/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tara Pilbrow Dance makes thoughtful and engaging dance theatre. We relate tales of daily life in a way that brings out their colour, contrast and emotional intensity. Our goal is to hang on to those fleeting moments of perfection and despair that are a part of every human experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every piece brings together movement, music and text to create a unique and narrative. We aim to create work that is sophisticated and intelligent, while ensuring that it is accessible to the widest possible audience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>